<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>NetSky</title>
<link>https://netsky.ai/posts.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://netsky.ai/posts.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>AI enabling every employee, not just developers.</description>
<generator>quarto-1.5.57</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Harnessing AI for Everyday Productivity</title>
  <dc:creator>Dylan Jones</dc:creator>
  <link>https://netsky.ai/posts/AppleLaunchBlog/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<center>
<h1>
Big AI News
</h1>
</center>
<p>Yesterday, on October 28, 2024 Apple launched iOS 18.1. With it, Apple Intelligence came to the masses. In the official opinion of NetSky AI, Apple intelligence represents the first AI product that represents a functional shift in the way that humans interact with their devices.</p>
<p>Apple Intelligence introduces features like automatic email and article summaries, a new way to navigate options menus, intelligent photo cleanup, and Smart Replies for streamlined communication. his launch highlights how AI is moving beyond novelty to become a practical tool for productivity—helping people focus on what matters rather than getting bogged down in repetitive tasks.</p>
<p>These tools allow people to immediately offload otherwise menial tasks with the click of a button, rather than navigating across several interfaces to generate something that the human could do better themselves. This is in stark contrast to tools like ChatGPT which, while useful, often feel more like enhanced search engines or quick writing aids than productivity powerhouses.</p>
<section id="its-not-all-sunshine-and-rainbows" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="its-not-all-sunshine-and-rainbows">It’s not all sunshine and rainbows</h2>
<p>Not all aspects of this release have been smooth. Early feedback from users online shows some comically poor summarizations from Apple’s local language models.</p>
<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://netsky.ai/posts/AppleLaunchBlog/AIbreakup.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>Apple Intelligence summarizing a breakup text</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<p>Running these models directly on user devices comes with trade-offs: Apple’s AI is managing to perform impressive tasks locally without freezing devices, but small language models still struggle with complex tasks. The limitations of current device processing mean that the accuracy of summaries, for example, still has room for improvement. And while it’s unlikely users want their phone to overheat or lag while summarizing an email, it’s clear that today’s mobile hardware can only go so far without the equivalent of a high-powered Nvidia GPU in their pockets.</p>
<p>Undoubtedly, users aren’t going to be ok with Siri overheating their phone for five plus minutes to summarize their email, so this is the best level of accuracy that 2024 can offer a local model without stuffing an NVidia RTX 4090 into your pocket.</p>
<p>Yet, in terms of user experience, Apple has achieved something unique. By building on familiar Siri commands and enhancing her intelligence, Apple has created a more cohesive personal assistant experience than any other consumer service currently offers. However, this version of Siri still has its limits: it’s great for helping with emails and appointments, but it isn’t yet capable of handling high-level computational tasks, like data analysis or complex scheduling across users. Those features may still be a few generations away.</p>
</section>
<section id="so-what-is-the-future-here" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="so-what-is-the-future-here">So what is the future here?</h2>
<p>Apple is undoubtedly on the right track—most people don’t care about the sophistication of AI models; they care about meaningful, immediate improvements in their lives. Apple Intelligence has made email and texting easier for millions. But as powerful as on-device AI has become, hardware limitations in 2024 mean it can only go so far.</p>
<p>It’s important to meet users where they are (their phones), but the hardware to accurately process their requests isn’t there yet in 2024.</p>
<p>Email, however, offers a scalable alternative for powerful AI integration. By allowing AI agents to process requests on remote servers, we can unleash the true potential of high-level computational power without device constraints. With email as the interface, users can enjoy rapid responses, sometimes within a minute—faster than most emails ever arrive. Through email, AI can access a user’s most relevant context and data, such as spreadsheets, presentations, and calendars, and act as a collaborative “colleague.” The only change that this represents in the workflow is the “to:” line of the collaboration between employees.</p>
<p>At NetSky AI, we believe this server-based AI solution is the best approach for personal assistance at scale. Email AI could be the assistant that every enterprise needs while being user-friendly enough for even the least tech-savvy users.</p>
<p>If you’d like to invest in AI tools that will turbocharge your actual work productivity (instead of just summarizing your text messages), <a href="founders@netsky.ai">email our founders</a> to learn how you can use our AI agents to act as a data analyst, outbound sales professional, or personal assistant for your business!</p>


</section>

<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>News</category>
  <category>Vision</category>
  <guid>https://netsky.ai/posts/AppleLaunchBlog/</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Launching NetSky AI</title>
  <dc:creator>Cody Peterson &amp; Dylan Jones</dc:creator>
  <link>https://netsky.ai/posts/founding/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<center>
<h1>
<strong>Introducing NetSky AI: Your All-in-One AI Email Assistant for Everyday Productivity</strong>
</h1>
</center>
<p>Today marks the launch of NetSky AI, a groundbreaking tool designed to transform email for non-technical users, putting the power of AI into your inbox to handle routine tasks with ease and precision. Whether it’s parsing spreadsheet data, coordinating calendar schedules across multiple users, or sending automated daily updates, NetSky AI offers an intuitive, hands-free approach to managing essential daily workflows or expeditiously handling one-off tasks you wish you could pass to an assistant.</p>
<p>We’ve all heard that AI will democratize the power of code for a new generation of workers, but with NetSky, the email inbox that you use every day becomes a development environment. Even your grandma can execute code to solve problems at work.</p>
<section id="why-netsky-ai" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="why-netsky-ai">Why NetSky AI?</h2>
<p>More than anything, NetSky is your boss’s personal assistant, at less than a fraction of the cost.</p>
<ul>
<li>Trying to find a meeting slot that works across 10 busy people’s schedules? NetSky can get permission to shuffle the entire team’s schedules to best align to their highest priority tasks.</li>
<li>Not sure what you should be doing? NetSky can read your emails to remind you of everything that you should be doing, and give some helpful steps to accomplish them!</li>
<li>Need a one-off report explaining what happened in your competition’s earnings call yesterday? That took your analyst all day, but NetSky can have that to you in 5 minutes.</li>
</ul>
<p>As a manager, why pay for one personal assistant when your entire team can have one for even less money?</p>
<p>NetSky AI is specifically crafted for non-technical users looking to get more from their email, without learning complex software. By embedding AI into day-to-day processes, NetSky helps users unlock efficiency in managing all sorts of tasks. Here’s what makes NetSky AI different:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Spreadsheet Parsing</strong>: Simply attach a spreadsheet, and NetSky AI will parse, analyze, and summarize data directly in your inbox, eliminating manual data handling.</li>
<li><strong>User Email Context</strong>: NetSky builds a database of your unique work, meaning that it will give you answers that are specified for your needs without endless ChatGPT prompting. Better yet, this is all stored while considering our industry leading privacy policy!</li>
<li><strong>Automated Scheduling and Calendar Coordination</strong>: When requested, NetSky can even negotiate across users, ensuring meetings are scheduled effortlessly, and your entire organization’s context is considered for optimal business outcomes.</li>
<li><strong>Daily Updates Delivered to Your Inbox</strong>: Configure NetSky to send end-of-day summaries or project status updates, keeping teams aligned without additional work. That daily newsletter your intern wrote is now 100% accurate and timely thanks to the consistency of code.</li>
<li><strong>Code Execution for Non-Programmers</strong>: Need to know what every website in the world is saying about your company? NetSky can execute a sentiment analysis. Tooling that was previously reserved for the tech savvy is now available to anyone that can write an email.</li>
</ul>
<p>As we launch, NetSky AI is committed to ongoing development that incorporates user feedback and expands on these core features, continually refining our approach to serve your productivity needs.</p>
</section>
<section id="whats-next" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="whats-next">What’s next?</h2>
<p>At NetSky, we’re not only developing a smarter email assistant but building a partner in productivity. Join us on this journey as we unlock new AI-powered capabilities that empower every user to manage their time, communications, and tasks more efficiently.</p>
<p>Welcome to the future of email with NetSky AI. We’re excited to share it with you!</p>


</section>

<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>company</category>
  <guid>https://netsky.ai/posts/founding/</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
